-Ma’am, I have to make a call.
Can you keep it down please?
-What?
-I mean, your voice.
-Please keep your voice down.
-my voice?
-are you asking me to keep my voice down?
-Yes please.
-Why?
-I have to make a phone call.
-I’m making a call.
-Alright.
-Please keep it down.
-I haven’t said anything.
-cool.
-Did you meet her?
-What happened next?
-aha
-Ma’am. I’m on the phone.
Please keep it down a little bit.
-Me?
-yes. I’m on the phone.
-Should I speak?
-No no you shouldn’t
-I haven’t said anything.
-Please.
-Did you go to the cafe
that I recommended to you?
-So?
-Hold on. Don’t hang up.
-Ma’am? I’m on the phone.
Please keep your voice down.
-I didn’t make any sound.
-Please keep it down.. I’m on the phone.
-you can speak after I hanging up.
please be real quiet.
-I haven’t said anything!
-Please ma’am..
-Ma’am? Ma’am?
-keep it down please.
lol
-I didn’t say anything.
-I’m on the phone! Please keep it down.
-It’s okay to use your phone.
-but.. please keep your voice down.
-I WON’T SAY ANYTHING.
-alright.
-Just keep it down. please.
lol
-I didn’t say anything
but why do you keep telling me to keep it down?
-please..
-Keep it down a little bit
-I DIDN’T SAY ANYTHING.
lol
-I don’t know what are you talking about.
-Ma’am. I’m so sorry
-We are filming a prank video.
-We’re Sucking Sunday on Youtube
-I really like your reaction.
-Camera is over there..
-Is it okay if you’re in the video?
-Sure.
-Thank you.
-Do you live nearby?